<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Home of mikepro</title>
    <link>https://mikepro.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Home of mikepro</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 25 Jan 2022 18:17:10 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://mikepro.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Comments via github</title>
      <link>https://mikepro.github.io/news/comments-via-github/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Jan 2022 18:17:10 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mikepro.github.io/news/comments-via-github/</guid>
      <description>It is now possible for you to add comments to this site via github issues and utterances.
Once you have authorised utterances to comment on your behalf you will be able to comment on any piece of content on this site.
Feel free to say hello below.
Why all the fuss? This whole website has been generated using hugo. A static site generator.
Hugo takes a series of articles and combines these with a set of HTML templates and produces HTML.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Welcome! to the home of mikepro</title>
      <link>https://mikepro.github.io/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Jan 2022 19:50:54 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mikepro.github.io/about/</guid>
      <description>Hallo, Bonjour, Witam, Ciao, こんにちは, Hello and welcome.
You have reached the personal site of github user mikepro otherwise known as Michael. A web developer and user of emacs.
One of my main aims with this website is to introduce emacs in a friendly and approachable way. Emacs has a fearsome reputation of having a step learning curve and being difficult to use. I can still remember the first time I opened up emacs (way back in 2001) and how overwhelmed I felt taking my first frustrating steps, getting confused, getting annoyed with cryptic keyboard shortcuts and not understanding what I was doing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Content coming soon</title>
      <link>https://mikepro.github.io/posts/my-first-post/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Jan 2022 19:20:29 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mikepro.github.io/posts/my-first-post/</guid>
      <description>Nothing to see here at the moment. I am working on adding some articles so come back soon.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
